(Sheldon:)Leonard, I've been working
on an opening joke
(Sheldon:)for our lecture at Berkeley.
(Leonard:)Oh, I like to laugh.
(Leonard:)But say it anyway.
(Sheldon:)Okay, um...
(Sheldon:)What do you say
to a graduate
(Sheldon:)of the UC Berkeley
physics department?
(Sheldon:)I'll have fries with that.
(chuckles)
(Sheldon:)Because his education
hasn't prepared him
(Sheldon:)for a career in the sciences.
(Penny:)You know, when they chase
you out of there,
(Penny:)you only have to run
faster than Sheldon.
(Amy:)Are you all set
for your trip?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I think so.
(Sheldon:)I just restocked the old PRK.
"PRK"?
(Leonard:)Public restroom kit.
(Leonard:)Everything a boy needs
for making pee pee
(Leonard:)in new and strange places.
(Sheldon:)I don't see what's crazy
about bringing a backpack
(Sheldon:)with your own toilet paper
and Purell.
(Leonard:)Keep going.
(Sheldon:)And rubber gloves,
uh, air freshener.
(Sheldon:)Um, noise-cancelling
headphones.
(Sheldon:)Oh, danger whistle.
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Sheldon:)pepper spray.
(Sheldon:)Ooh, a multi-language
"occupied" sign.
(Sheldon:)Uh, let's see.
(Sheldon:)We have seat protectors,
uh, booties for my shoes,
(Sheldon:)a clothespin for my nose.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and a mirror on a stick,
(Sheldon:)so I can make sure the person
in the stall next to me
(Sheldon:)isn't some kind of weirdo.
(Penny:)You still worried some Berkeley
girl is gonna steal him away?
(Amy:)Yes, who do you think gave him
the danger whistle?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪